okay so let's look at our issue quiz
solution we have these two instructions
to issue this is the older one to issue
so we're going to get a divide or
multiply reservation station Mark that
this is a
divide FS1 and FS2 are needed as
parameters look here you find that RS 4
and rs1 are going to produce that value
so we don't get any values from the
register file and then we're going to
update for F4 that the result is going
to come out of RS5 and now we're done
with this instruction this instruction
cannot issue because it's a
multiplication instruction all of the
divide multiply reservation stations are
busy so until one of these finishes this
instruction isn't going to issue so now
our issue part is going to be stalled
until that is result